Guide to the Papers of Abby Weed Grey 1922-1978 MC.151
New York University Archives
- Series XVII: Abby Weed Grey Photographs
  - Subseries A: Exhibitions 1962-1972
    - Communication Thru Art, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - "Composition" Bertha Bonart, AWGP_CTA_15_8_9 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - "Structures No. 6" Leonard Barkin, AWGP_CTA_15_8_10 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - "Evening Lights" Ralph Avery, AWGP_CTA_15_8_11 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 11)
      - "Head of a Man" Richard Arnold, AWGP_CTA_15_8_12 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 12)
      - "Summer" Milford Apetz, AWGP_CTA_15_8_13 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 13)
      - "A Valediction of Weeping" June Wayne, AWGP_CTA_15_8_14 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 14)
      - "We are Tapers too" June Wayne, AWGP_CTA_15_8_15 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 15)
      - "Mirror" Beth Van Hoesen, AWGP_CTA_15_8_16 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 16)
      - "Profile" Beth Van Hoesen, AWGP_CTA_15_8_17 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 17)
      - "Cynthia" Beth Van Hoesen, AWGP_CTA_15_8_18 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 18)
      - "Goldilocks" Sinton, AWGP_CTA_15_8_19 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 19)
      - "The Wedding" Ariel Parkinson, AWGP_CTA_15_8_20 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 20)
      - "The Family" Nancy Genn, AWGP_CTA_15_8_21 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 21)
      - "Draped Woman in Room", AWGP_CTA_15_8_22 (Box 38, Folder 8, Item 22)
    - 1st Triennale of World Art, India, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Communication Thru Art, Indian Tour, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - M.A.P. Party, Jan 11, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Communication Thru Art, S. India, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 10 Young American Artists, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225402 2
    - Communication Thru Art, India, Book Presentation, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - MCAD Exhibition, Installation, 1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Turkish Art, SUNY Binghamton, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Contemporary Turkish Painting, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - One World Thru Art, Installation, Minn State Fair, Jun 7, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - One World Thru Art -mounted, Jun 7, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - One World Thru Art -mounted, Jun 7, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Subseries B: Personal and Publicity
    - Benjamin Grey & Abby Weed Grey-Early, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225403 0
    - Abby Weed Grey-Publicity, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Abby Weed Grey & Thomas Waite-curator, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Deqhani-Tafti, Hassam (Angelican Bishop of Iran), undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Additions, undated (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Additions (Publicity), Undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Grey Gallery-St. Paul
    - Grey Gallery at 4997 Otis St., St. Paul, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Subseries D: Grey Gallery-NYU
    - Opening & Collateral, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Grey Art Gallery & 3rd Floor Main, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Iranian Art Today, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Lion Rug Exhibit, undated (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Tanavoli Exhibit, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Works Donated, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Subseries E: Artist Photos
    - Communication Thru Art, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Aslier, Mustafa & Berk, Nurullah-Turkey, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
      General
      The man identified as Nurullah Berk in the image may be somebody else.
    - Ayden, Necat-Turkey, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Berger, Aliye-Turkey, undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225404 8
    - Eyuboglu, Bedri Rahmi, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Golzari, Behrooz-Iran, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Jamshid, Khagam; Siah, Armanjami; Parviz, Tanavoli, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Koral, Fureya-Turkey, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Kut, Mushin-Turkey, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Varlik, Utku-Turkey, undated (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Subseries F: Tanavoli, Parviz
    - Miscellaneous-Publicity Photos, undated (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Foundry at University of Tehran, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Tanavoli Bronze-Pahlavi University, Shraz, Iran, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Tanavoli with 2 children, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Tanavoli Art work, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Subseries G: Artwork
    - Grey Collection Art, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Guinis, Alkis (Greek Artist), undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Padamsee, Akbar (Indian Artist), undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Artwork (Seichrist, Ron), undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Subseries H: Miscellaneous
    - Contact Sheets, undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Nov 4, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Nov 10, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Nov 23, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, Dec 1, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      3 1142 04225405 5
    - Student Sculpture Party, Feb 1, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Traveling with the Bishop of Iran (Evangelism in a Moslem world), 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Blind Students of Braille School, Isfahan, Iran, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Snapshots, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)